Finding Aid for the John Egerton Papers - Estate Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Projects
  - Projects - Logan County, Kentucky Project, 2010 - Proposals (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Projects - Education for the Disadvantaged, 2010 - Martha O’Brien Center (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Projects - Word Bank, 2010 - Egerton’s Notes on Writing (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Community Food Advocates, 2009 - “Everybody Eats” Website, Correspondence, Outgoing, March 22, 2009-April 6, 2009 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Community Food Advocates - “Everybody Eats” Website, Planning (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Community Food Advocates - “Everybody Eats” Website, Planning (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Community Food Advocates - “Everybody Eats” Website Planning (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Community Food Advocates 2010 - Communication and Marketing Plans (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Community Food Advocates, 2011 - Lunch at Arnold’s Country Kitchen (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Community Food Advocates, 2011 - Taste of Music City Festival (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Community Food Advocates, 2011 - Food Summit, 2011 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Community Food Advocates, 2012 - Nashville Food Project Dinner (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Community Food Advocates, 2012 - The State of the Barbecue Nation (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Community Food Advocates, 2012 - Growing Heathy Kids (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Community Food Advocates, 2011-2012 - Grants programs (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Community Food Advocates, 2011-2013 - Board Members Notebook (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Community Food Advocates, 2011-2013 - Board Meeting Minutes (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Community Food Advocate, 2011-2013 - Financial Statements (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Community Food Advocates, 2011-2013 - Clippings (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Community Food Advocates, 2011-2013 - Clippings (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Projects - Edmundson Cemetery Projects, 2011 - Confidential Report (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Projects - Self-Publishing and E-Books, 2011 - Research and Planning (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Projects - Nashville Encyclopedia, 2013 - Proposal (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Projects - Coalition of Immokalee Workers, 2013 - Notes and Egerton’s Participation in Protest March Florida (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Writings
  - Writing Ideas - Articles, 1960s - Hospital Notes (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Writing Ideas - Articles, 1960s-1980s - General (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Writing ideas - Articles, 1960s-1970s - General (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Writing ideas - Articles, 1960s-1970s - General (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Writing Ideas - Articles, 1970s - General (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Writing Ideas - Articles, 1970s—Ideas for Southern Voices (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Writing Ideas - Articles, 1975 - Politics and Country Music (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Writing ideas - Articles, 1976 - Smithsonian Family Histories (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Writing ideas - Articles, 1980s - General (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Writing Ideas - Articles, 1980s-1990s - General, plus Employment Possibilities (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Writing Ideas - Articles, 1980s-1990s - General (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Writing Ideas - Articles, 1990s - General (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Writing Ideas - Articles, 1995 - Political and Social Commentary (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Writing Ideas - Articles, 1997-1998 - Bill Moyers (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Writing Ideas - Articles, 1997-1998 - Changes in the Episcopal Church (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Writing Ideas - Articles, 1999 - The New Southerners (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Writing Ideas - Articles, 1999 - Bill Clinton (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Writing ideas - Articles, 2002 - State Elections, 2002 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Writing ideas - Articles, 2002 - State Elections, 2002 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Writing Ideas - Articles, 2002 - National Election, 2002 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Writing Ideas - Book, 1970s-1980s - General (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Writing Ideas - Book, 1970s-2000s - General (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Writing Ideas - Book, 1980 - City History Books and Services as a Consultant (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Writing ideas - Book, 1980s - Spin-off Book Ideas following the Publication of Speak Now Against the Day (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Writing Ideas - Book, 1990s-2000s - Living in the Stacks of the Library of Congress (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Writing Ideas - Book, 1995 - Tennessee Writers Collection (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Writing Ideas - Book, 1999 - American Inventory: The Making of the 2000 Census (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Writing Ideas - Book, 2000 - Unfinished Song: A Year in the Life of Nashville (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Writing Ideas - Book, 2006 - Waffle House (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Writing Ideas - 1960s Correspondence with Agents and Editors - Incoming, Anderson - Vincent (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Writing Ideas - 1970s Correspondence with Agents and Editors - Incoming, Adler-Wyle (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Writing Ideas - 1980s-2000s Correspondence with Agents and Editors, Incoming - Anderson-Lynch (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Writing Ideas - 1980s-2000s - Correspondence with Agents and Editors, Incoming - Machemer-Wolf (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Writing Ideas - Correspondence with Agents and Editors - Outgoing - October 24, 1966-August 12, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Writing Ideas - Correspondence with Agents and Editors - Outgoing - December 9, 1980-July 6, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Writing Ideas - Correspondence with Agents and Editors - Outgoing - July 21, 1981-October 18, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Writings - Master’s Thesis, 1960 - “Some Aspects of the Relationships between the State and the State Government” (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Writings - Booklet, 1960 - “Operation Indonesia” (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Writings - Articles, 1960-1964 - Bicentennial Reports of the University of Southern Florida (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Writings - Articles, 1963-1964 - Miscellaneous Articles printed in Florida Newspapers (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Writings - Articles, 1965 - “The New Missionary”, The Christian Century. (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Writings - Articles, 1967 - “Little Rock Ten Years Later”, The Saturday Review (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Writings - Articles, 1967 - Jesse Stuart (Incomplete article) (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Writings - Articles, 1970 - “The Louisville Story, 1970”, Race Relations Reporter (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Writings - Articles, 1972 - “That New South”, The Progressive (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Writings - Articles, 1974 - “Duke University”, Change (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Writings - Articles, 1977 - “Notes from Sue Alston”, Hampshire Plantation, South Carolina (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Writings - Articles, 1982 - “The South and the Nation”, Atlanta Magazine (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Writings - Articles, 1980s - Proposed articles on the Writers of Girard, Kansas (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Writings - Articles, 1980s - Proposed Articles on the Writers of Girard, Kansas (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Writings - Articles, 1985 - “I Am What I Am”, Homewords: A Book of Tennessee Writers (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Writings - Articles, 1884-1987 - “Robert H. Allen”, Tennessee (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Writings - Articles, 1988 - “Poverty Palace” and other articles re The Southern Poverty Law Center (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Writings - Articles, 1988 - The Southern Poverty Law Center, Correspondence, Incoming - Belak-Williams (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Writings - Articles, 1988 - The Southern Poverty Law Center, Correspondence, Outgoing - May 17, 1988-July 24, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Writings - Articles, 1988 - The Southern Poverty Law Center - Research and Notes (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Writings - Articles, 1988 - The Southern Poverty Law Center - Research (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Writings - Articles, 1995 - “South Carolina Politics”, The New York Times Magazine (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Writings - Articles, 1996 - “Faces in the Crowd”, The Tennessean, April-October, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Writings - Articles, 1995-1998 - Proposed Articles for The New Yorker (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Writings - Articles, 1966 and 1998 - “White Minority Governs with Force”, The Tennessean and 1998 Article on Zimbabwe, missing one page (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Writings - Articles, 1995-1998 - Research for Articles on Zimbabwe (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Writings - Articles, 1998 - Proposed Articles on South Africa (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Writings - Articles, 2004 - “The Gravity of Segregation”, typescript (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Writings - Article, 2004 - “The Gravity of Segregation”, Southern Education Foundation (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Writings - Articles, 2004 - “Where We Stand” (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Writings - Articles, 2004 - “The People vs, George Bush” (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Writings - Articles, 2004 - “The People vs, George Bush”, Research Notes (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Writings - Articles, 2005 - “No Grits, No Glory: The Endurance of Southern Food”, Oxford American (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Writings - Articles, 2008 - “Barbecue”, The New Encyclopedia of Southern Culture (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Writings - Articles, 2009 - A Tribute to John Hope Franklin, Fisk University (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Writings - Articles, 2010 - “Tomato Haiku”, chapter 16 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Writings - Articles, 2013 - “Moon Pies and Memories”, Southern Cultures (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Writings - Articles, Undated or Untitled on Education (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Writings - Articles, Undated or Untitled on Politics (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Writings - Books, 1963 - A Bridge from Darkness, Typescript of Unpublished Novel (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Writings - Books, 1974 - The Americaniztion of Dixie, Review (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Writings - Books, 1982 - Paradise Island, unpublished - Correspondence, Incoming-Arnovitz-Pulitzer (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Writings - Books, 1982 - Paradise Island, unpublished - Correspondence, Outgoing, April 7, 1975-March 22, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Writings - Books, 1982 - Paradise Island, unpublished - Readers’ Reports (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Writings - Books, 1982 - Paradise Island, unpublished - typescript, Chapters 1-14 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Writings - Books, 1982 - Paradise Island, unpublished - typescript, Chapters 15-24 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Writings - Books, 1982 - Paradise Island, unpublished - typescript, Chapters 25-37 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Writings - Books, 1982 - Paradise Island, unpublished - typescript, Chapters 1-4 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Writings - Books, 1982 - Paradise Island, unpublished - typescript, Chapters 5-11 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Writings - Books, 1982 - Paradise Island, unpublished - typescript, Chapters 12-20 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Writings - Books, 1983 - Generations - Correspondence, Incoming - Baskins-Walther (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Writings - Books, 1983 - Generations - Correspondence, Outgoing-August 3, 1993-June 12, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Writings - Books, 1983 - Generations - Contracts and Royalty Statements for Paperback Edition (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Writings - Books, 1983 - Generations - Research Materials (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Writings - Books, 1983 - Generations - Publicity (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Writings - Books, 1983 - Generations - Japanese Translation (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Writings - Books, 1987 - Southern Food - Handwritten Corrections to Proof Pages (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Writings - Books, 1987 - Southern Food - Research—Recipes (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Writings - Books, 1987 - Southern Food - Research—Restaurants-Tennessee (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Writings - Books, 1987 - Southern Food - Research - Restaurants-Georgia, Alabama, Mississippi (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Writings - Books, 1987 - Southern Food—Research - Restaurants-North Carolina, South Carolina, Virginia, Florida (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Writings - Books, 1987 - Southern Food - Research - Restaurants-Louisiana, Arkansas, Kentucky, Texas (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Writings - Books, 1987 - Southern Food - Research - Restaurants-Inside and Outside the South (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Writings - Books, 1987 - Southern Food - Information about Cookbooks (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Writings - Books, 1994 - Speak Now Against the Day - Correspondence, Incoming - Adams-Sitton (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Writings - Books, 1994 - Speak Now Against the Day - Correspondence, Outgoing - January 6, 1994-July 12, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Writings - Books, 1994 - Speak Now Against the Day - Planning (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Writings - Books, 1994 - Speak Now Against the Day - Research Materials (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Writings - Books, 1994 - Speak Now Against the Day - Requests for Permission to Use Materials (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Writings - Books, 1994 - Speak Now Against the Day - Publicity (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Writings - Books, 1994 - Speak Now Against the Day - Reviews (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Writings - Books, 2006 - Ali Dubyiah and the Forty Thieves - Research Materials (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Writings - Books, 2006 - Ali Dubyiah and the Forty Thieves - Research Materials (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Writings - Books, 2006 - Ali Dubyiah and the Forty Thieves - Research Materials (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Writings - Books, 2006 - Ali Dubyiah and the Forty Thieves - Notes (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Writings - Books, 2006 - Ali Dubyiah and the Forty Thieves - Notes (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Writings - Books, 2006 - Ali Dubyiah and the Forty Thieves - Notes (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Writings - Books, 2006 - Ali Dubyiah and the Forty Thieves - Planning (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Writings - Books, 2006 - Ali Dubyiah and the Forty Thieves - Contract and Marketing Plans (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Writings - Books, 2006 - Ali Dubyiah and the Forty Thieves - Cover Art by Bill Sanders (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Writings - Books, 2006 - Ali Dubyiah and the Forty Thieves - First Drafts (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Writings - Books, 2006 - Ali Dubyiah and the Forty Thieves - Complete First Draft, Edited April, 2006 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Writings - Books, 2006 - Ali Dubiyah and the Forty Thieves - Typescript, Edited September, 2006 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Writings - Books, 2006 - Ali Dubyiah and the Forty Thieves - Galley Proofs, Edited (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Writings - Books, 2006 - Ali Dubyiah and the Forty Thieves - Complete Manuscript with Notes (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Writings - Books, 2006 - Ali Dubyiah and the Forty Thieves - Two Copies of the Book, plus The Last American by J.R. Mitchell (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Writings - Books, 2006 - Ali Dubyiah and the Forty Thieves - Reviews (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Writings - Books, 2006 - Ali Dubyiah and the Forty Thieves - Typescript of Introduction (Framed Cover Art of Ali Dubyiah and the Forty Thieves signed by the Artist Bill Sanders located at 21 North Art Rack) (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Writings - Books, 2009 - The New Lovin’ Spoonfuls (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Writings - Books, 2009-2011 - The Sausage Papers - Research Materials (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Writings - Books, 2009 - Political Poetry, 2009 - Collection of poems by Egerton (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Writings - Book Jackets for Miscellaneous Books by John Egerton (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Writings - Miscellaneous Memorial Tributes for Others written by Egerton, 1987-2011 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Writings - The Tennessean, 1996 - a Series of Three Articles about Nashville School Integration (Article #3 missing) (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Writings - The Tennessean, 1996 - Research Materials for Integration Articles (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Writings - The Tennessean, 1996 - Research Materials for Integration Articles (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Writings - The Tennessean, 1996 - Article about Richard Benjamin, Superintendent of Metro Nashville Public Schools (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Writings - Books, 2001 - Co-Editor, Nashville - Research Materials (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Writings - Books, 2001 - Co-Editor, Nashville - Research Materials (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Writings - Books, 2001 - Co-Editor, Nashville - Research Materials (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Writings - Books, 2001 - Co-Editor, Nashville - Research Materials (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Writings - Books, 2001 - Co-Editor, Nashville - Research Materials (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Writings - Books, 2001 - Co-Editor, Nashville - Research Materials (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Writings - Books, 2001 - Co-Editor, Nashville - Research Materials (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Writings - Books, 2001 - Co-Editor, Nashville - Research Materials (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Writings - Books, 2001 - Co-Editor, Nashville - Research Materials (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Writings - Books, 2001 - Co-Editor, Nashville - Research Materials (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Writings - Books, 2001 - Co-Editor, Nashville - Research Materials (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Writings - Books, 2001 - Co-Editor, Nashville - Correspondence, Incoming - Ames-Heard (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Writings - Books, 2001 - Co-Editor, Nashville - Correspondence, Incoming - Horton-Siles (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Writings - Books, 2001 - Co-Editor, Nashville - Correspondence, Incoming - Watson-Wood (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Writings - Books, 2001 - Co-Editor, Nashville - Correspondence, Outgoing - July 6, 2000-December 29, 2009 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Writings - Books, 2001 - Co-Editor, Nashville - Business e-mails between John Egerton and Others, Arranged Chronologically September, 27, 2000-June 1, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - writings - Books, 2001 - Co-Editor, Nashville - Planning (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Writings - Books, 2001 - Co-Editor, Nashville - Planning (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Writings - Books, 2001 - Co-Editor, Nashville - Contracts, 2000-2005 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Writings — Books, 2001 - Co-Editor, Nashville - Sales and Distribution Data (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Writings - Books, 2001 - Co-Editor, Nashville - Sales and Distribution Data (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Writings - Books, 2001 - Co-Editor, Nashville - Sales and Distribution Data (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Writings - Books, 2001 - Co-Editor, Nashville - Sales and Distribution Data (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Writings - Books, 2001 - Co-Editor, Nashville - Sales and Distribution Data (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Writings - Books- 2001 - Co-Editor, Nashville - Book Jackets and Promotional Material (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Writings - Books, 2013 - Great Hearts - Nashville School Desegregation (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Writings - “Living Downtown” - Series of Articles for The Tennessean, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Writings - “Living Downtown” - Research Materials (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Writings - “Living Downtown - Research Materials (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Writings - Plans for a Foreword by John Egerton for a Proposed Book by Will Campbell, 2002 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Writings - Cornbread Nation, 2002, edited by John Egerton - Reviews (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Writings - Foreword by John Egerton for The Jemima Code, by Toni Tipton Martin, 2009 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Writings - Editor, Home to Us, 2012 by Varina Willsee and Nancy Rhoda - E-mails and Correspondence (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Writings - Editor, Home to Us, 2012 by Varina Willsee and Nancy Rhoda - Research Materials (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Writings - Editor, Home to Us, 2012 by Varina Willsee and Nancy Rhoda - Manuscript Drafts (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Writings - Editor, Home to Us, 2012 by Varina Wllsee and Nancy Rhoda - Page Proofs (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Writings - Editor, Home to Us, 2012 by Varina WIllsee and Nancy Rhoda - Page Proofs (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Writings - Editor, Home to Us, 2012 by Varina Willsee and nancy Rhoda - Planning and Marketing (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Writings - Review of The Faulkner Newsletter, 1994 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Writings - Endorsement Comments for Biscuit Bliss, 2004, by James by W.O. Smith by (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Writings - Blurb for The Wind Done Gone, 2000 by Alice Randall (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Writings by Others - Dixie: The South in an Age of Change, Tulane University, 1981 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Writings by Others - Kinfolks by Jo Carson, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Writings by Others - Highlander by Eliot Wigginton, 1989 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Writings by Others - Dissertation on Will Campbell by Robin by W.O. Smiot (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Writings by Others - Dissertation on Will Campbell by Robin Jimmerson, 1990 - Pp. 115-299 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Writings by Others - Hat in Hand and Throbbing Heart by E. Clayton Braddock, Jr., 1991 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Writings by Others - Sideman by W.O. Smith, 1991 - Manuscript and Diskettes (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Writings by Others - Sideman by W.O. Smith, 1991 - Planning (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Writings by Others - Sideman by W.O. Smith, 1991 - Marketing and Reviews (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Writings by Others - Sideman by W.O. Smith, 1991 - Memorial Concert (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Writings by Others - Roy B. Herron by Roy B. Herron, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Writings by Others - Materials on Fruit of the Land by Alice Cobb, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Writings by Others - A Researcher’s Guide to the John Egerton File on the Johns Committee by James Schnur, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Writings by Others - The Carmack-Cooper Shooting by James Summerville, 1994 - Pp. 1-111 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Writings by Others - The Carmack-Cooper Shooting by James Summerville, 1994 - Pp. 112-211 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Writings by Others - A Book of Names by Clayton Braddock, 1994 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Writings by Others - Mountain Country Cooking by Mark Sohn - Pp. 1-198 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Writings by Others - Mountain Country Cooking by Mark Sohn - Pp. 199-455 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Writings by Others - Covenant by Will Campbell and Al Clayton, 1989 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Writings by Others - ‘Black Power’ and the Roots of the African American Freedom Struggle by Timothy Tyson, 1998 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Writings by Others - Annie by Dana Wildsmith, 1999 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Writings by Others - A Beautiful Woman Is Always with Someone by Dana Wildsmith, 2000 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Writings by Others - The Diffusionists Have Landed by Marc R. Stengel, 2000 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Writings by Others - The Silence at Boalt Hall by Andrea Guerreo, 2000 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Writings by Others - Just the Facts, M’am by Douglas D. Cumming, 2001 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Writings by Others - Facing Facts, Facing South by Douglas D. Cumming, 2002 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Writings by Others - The Dixie Bee Line Highway by Linda Negro, 2002 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Writings by Others - Looking for Good Will by Scott Price, 2003 - Pp. 1-69 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Writings by Others - Looking for Good Will by Scott Price, 2003—Pp. 70-140 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Writings by Others - Looking for Good Will by Scott price, 2003—Pp. 141-210 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Writings by Others - Looking for Good Will by Scott Price, 2003 - Pp. 211-255, plus Letters (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Writings by Others - Materials Pertaining to a Proposed Biography of John J. Hooker, Sr. by Jay Hamburg, 2003 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Writings by Others - Glimpses of God and Country, Jack E. Brown, 2005 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Writings by Others - Sketches by Jack E. Brown, 2005 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Writings by Others - Edna Lewis, Repast, Fall 2007 by Damon Lee Fowler (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Writings by Others - Random Thoughts by Bill Peach, 2008 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Writings by Others - Materials Pertaining to Judge Joseph Holt by Susan B. Dyer, 2009 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Writings by Others - Proposal for Chronicles of the Cumberland Settlements by Paul Clements, 2009 (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Writings by Others - Proposal for Socialists in Nashville by Gene TeSelle, 2009 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Writings by Others - Thirteen Poems for Five Bypasses by Brenda Butka, 2010 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Writings by Others - Light from Carolina by Rachel Lawson, 2011 - Manuscript and CD (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Writings by Others - Hollywood, Tennessee by Bobby Braddock, 2012 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Writings by Others - The Cardboard Castle by Holly Roberts, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Writings by Others - 1815 by Tony Dunbar, n.d. - Pp. 1-104 (Box 32, Folder 6)